

Andrii Golub

Middle frontend developer

Kyiv, Ukraine andrewgolub25@gmail.com https://t.me/flokiowl https://flokiowl.herokuapp.com

Summary of Qualifications

I have been working in the field of IT for about 3 years. During this time I have been involved in a number of commercial software projects, business applications with client-server and web technologies. Designed and implemented components for several projects. I work well in a team. I currently work as a frontend developer at RegToEvent.

Skills

HTML&CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Git

Experience

RegToEvent - Middle Frontend Developer

(2 years 9 months)

11.2020 - current (1 year 9 months)

Tech: HTML&CSS, SASS, JavaScript, VueJS, Git

Description:

Project Lndli: Service for creating landing pages and bio-links. Bio links are the new personal websites. Platforms like Instagram, Twitter, and TikTok only allow one link in a bio. Using a biography allows you to link to all pages - websites, social media posts, videos, music - making it easier to find an audience for all content.

Project LMSka: Creation of a learning management system (LMS) for online schools, business trainers and private companies (onboarding). The tool provides a lesson designer, payment for courses, a personal account for students, homework and assessments, issuing certificates.

Project RegToEvent: Development of a CRM system for event managers and event organizers that solves the entire range of tasks: event creation (including online events), ticket creation, landing page designer, participant registration, payment acceptance, participant check-in, statistics collection.

SOFTPRO - Junior Frontend Developer

07.2019 - 07.2020 (1 year)

Tech: HTML&CSS, LESS, JavaScript, Jquery, Handlebars, SQL

Description:

Development and support of online stores, online pharmacies, open data geoportals.

Education

National University of Food Technologies

2013 - 2017

Faculty: hotel, restaurant and tourism business

Languages

English - Intermediate